but the point here is that we wanted to retouch. So I can come to retouch and we have the methods of
object or spot. So I use this spot method and as you see we have healer, we have clone stamp,
we have blur and we have burn or dodge, right? So if you are aware or if you do have the experience
of working with Adobe Photoshop, you're aware of all of these tools you probably are because
these are the most basic photo retouching tools when it comes to Adobe Photoshop, you know?
And we also have gone through that in the Photoshop course of the take-off college about these
tools, each of them and what each do and the identity of them. But all you need to do,
all you need to know over here is that these are the appropriate tools when it comes to retouching,
right? And for example, if I use the healer or repairer and I click and drag,
so it's not drag-able, it's just clickable, right? But if I click, as you see, for example, I click here,
this is removed, right? Or I click here and I see this one is removed as well, right? So we can use this one
or other retouching tools that we have over here.